{
    "id": "8d323736f6314637914e5cba4eb69746",
    "title": "Conjunctions vs. Prepositions",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b09111567c7649bfa4eb0aef6ce1e0ff",
            "title": "Joining Words Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I will not come …………………….. you need me.",
                    "description": "Unless is similar to if…not.",
                    "answers": [
                        "without",
                        "unless",
                        "whether"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will not go ………………………. you do.",
                    "description": "Unless is a conjunction it is used before a clause without is a preposition. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "without",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She looks …………………… her mother.",
                    "description": "Like is a preposition. It is used with nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do ……………………… I say.",
                    "description": "As is a conjunction it is used before a clause.",
                    "answers": [
                        "as",
                        "like"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………… I received the message, I started.",
                    "description": "As soon as is used to mean that one action commenced immediately after another action.",
                    "answers": [
                        "As soon as",
                        "No sooner",
                        "Hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I take no more ………………………. I give.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "then",
                        "compared to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Scarcely had he gone ………………………. his friends arrived.",
                    "description": "Either when or before is possible here. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "when",
                        "before"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He lost not only his ticket …………………….. his passport.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "but",
                        "but also",
                        "also"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He washed ………………… his hands nor his mouth.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "neither",
                        "either",
                        "or"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will not go ……………………….. you.",
                    "description": "Without is a preposition. It is used before a noun/pronoun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He succeeded ……………………….. his hard work.",
                    "description": "Because of is used before a noun/pronoun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "because",
                        "because of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. his hard work, he could not succeed.",
                    "description": "In spite of and despite are interchangeable. These words are used before a noun/pronoun.",
                    "answers": [
                        "In spite of",
                        "Despite",
                        "Although",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}